Justin W. Eastin

Full-Stack Web Developer with skills in time management, problem-solving, and building processes. Creating products in a growing industry for people to appreciate. Experience with HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Python and Angular.

Jacksonville, FL 32210 (904) 708-7561 JWEastin199@gmail.com www.github.com/DrixaBoi www.linkedin.com/in/jweastin

PROJECTS

MyFlix Angular Client —

Built using Angular CLI and was an introduction to Typescript. Created and hosted the database on Heroku. It is an educational project, where users create an account, browse movies, and receive information about the director, genres, and description.

PokéMon PokéDex —

Used Javascript, Jquery, and an external API/third party API integration to present the user with a list of searchable Pokémon they could select to receive a modal pop-up of more information.

<u>Meet Aρρ</u> —

My introduction to test-driven development. React.js App users can search nearby cities for events, and with an authentication, welcome screen users can pass with their google accounts.

EXPERIENCE

Palagio, Jacksonville, FL — Sous Chef / Kitchen Manager

October 2020 - December 2021

- Manage day-to-day operations, menu building, ordering, preparation, time management, and food storage/safety.
- Direct and train kitchen staff and waitresses, create schedules and take customer feedback.

Olympus Ranch, Salt Lake City, Ut — Sous Chef

2014 - 2018

- Direct kitchen staff and workflow in the afternoon and evening hours, Ordering and taking stock of supplies.
- Feeding 250-300 residents, providing four options for each service as well as an open menu for any time meal choices.

SKILLS

- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Node.js
- React
- Angular
- Python
- AWS
- Heroku
- MongoDB
- RESTful API
- Problem Solving
- Time Management
- Collaboration
- Customer Relations
- Adaptability

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry, Certificate in Full-Stack Development

January 2022 - July 2022 Introduction to Front-End Development, and Full-Stack Immersion courses.

Free CodeCamp.org, Free online courses

May 2022 - Ongoing
Free course classes in
Python, Javascript, React,
and Angular.